<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ツールバーサンプル</string>
    <string name="tv_article">Accessibility Material Design　linkCopy link　Accessibility by default is a foundational design value for Material. Understanding and anticipating a wide range of human experiences and disabilities establishes product foundations that prevent costly redesigns, reduce tech and design debt, and conserve resources upfront.　Accessibility standards built into Material components are designed to provide a foundation for inclusive product design. Understanding your product’s accessibility can enhance usability for all users, including those with low vision, blindness, hearing impairments, cognitive impairments, motor impairments, or situational disabilities (such as a broken arm).　linkCopy link　Get started　linkCopy link　Accessibility requirements and goals are documented across component pages and guidelines. In component guidance, accessibility standards are both implicit (built into design and code), as well as explicit (considerations are discussed where judgment is required.)　Use this page as a starting point for understanding the accessibility standards applied across Material guidelines, as well as a reference to continue checking throughout design and development stages.　linkCopy link　Principles for accessible design　The following principles for accessible design are approaches that can help anticipate, include, and respond to the needs of individuals. linkCopy link　Learn before, not after　Before defining solutions, invest time in understanding the needs of users with a wide range of abilities and life experiences. Formal and informal research can open new ways of thinking, reduce biases, and encourage creative ways to make access available, especially to those who fall outside prevailing norms.　Accessible design processes anticipate as many potential product or experience outcomes as possible upfront. When design problems arise, the exploration of outcomes can be used as a research foundation for learning and recovering thoughtfully.　linkCopy link　Requirements as a starting point　The minimum requirements established by WCAG support specific human needs. Designing with accessibility standards is a creative opportunity to expand and improve the application of requirements that improve human relationships with technology.　History has shown that features originating from responses to specific access needs (dark mode, text-to-speech, speech-to-text) are a result of creative problem-solving within specified constraints. Seeing the requirements as opportunities, rather than constraints, has been shown to lead to solutions that ultimately serve many.</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title">Material!</string>
    <string name="toolbar_subtitle">ツールバーを使用</string>
</resources>